(Sheldon:)...she arranged for me to be
an Amtrak Junior Conductor for the day.
(Sheldon:)It's usually only open to children.
She got them to make an exception.
(Leonard:)Shame on her.
(Sheldon:)They let me blow the whistle,
Leonard.
(Leonard:)She's good.
l know. And it gets worse.
(Sheldon:)Her efforts are causing me
to have affectionate feelings for her...
(Sheldon:)...at inappropriate times.
(Leonard:)You mean like in bed
or in the shower?
No. And would you please stop
referencing that infernal book?
(Sheldon:)For example, this morning...
...l was calculating the random motion
of virtual particles in a vacuum...
(Sheldon:)...when suddenly, the particles morphed
into an image of Amy's dandruff...
(Sheldon:)...gently cascading down onto her pale,
slightly hunched shoulders.